<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eduthon-Aimers</string>
    <string name="h4">Blink</string>
    <string name="h3">Exercise Your Eyes</string>
    <string name="h1">Comfortable Lighting</string>
    <string name="h2">Reduce glare</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="glare">1)Reflections on your computer screen as well as glare on walls and reflective surfaces cause CVS
\n2) Install an anti-glare screen on your monitor
\n3) Paint bright white walls a darker colour with a matte finish
\n4) Cover the windows
    </string>
    <string name="blink">1) Blinking moistens eyes &amp; prevents dryness and irritation
    \n2) People blink less frequently while working at a computer
    </string>
    <string name="exc">1).Every 20 minutes, blink 10 times by closing your eyes as if falling asleep - very slowly.
        This will help rewet your eyes.
\n2).Look far away at an object for 10-15 seconds, then stare at something up close for 10-15 seconds.
        Then look back at the distant object. Do this 10 times. This exercise decreases the risk of your eyes
        focusing ability to lock up (accommodative spasm) after lengthy computer work
    </string>
    <string name="light">1) Reduce outdoor light by closing drapes or blinds
    \n2) Excessively bright light either from harsh interior lighting or sunlight coming in through a window can cause eye strain
    \n3) Position the computer monitor or screen so windows are to the side instead of in front or behind it
    </string>
    <string name="d1">Drink at least one glass of water before each lecture</string>
    <string name="d2">Set reminders</string>
    <string name="d3">Keep a reusable water bottle with you</string>
    <string name="d4">Replace other drinks with water</string>

    <string name="dd1">A simple way to increase your water intake is to make a habit of drinking at least one glass of water before each lecture</string>
    <string name="dd2">You can also set reminders to drink more water.
        These reminders can help you increase your water intake specially if you struggle with being forgetful or too busy to drink.
    </string>
    <string name="dd3">Keeping a water bottle with you throughout the day can help you drink more water.
    Keeping a water bottle handy can also serve as a visual reminder to drink more water. If you see the bottle on your desk or table
        you will constantly be reminded to drink more.</string>
    <string name="dd4">One way to drink more water and boost your health and reduce your calorie intake
    is to replace other drinks such as soda and sports drinks with water.
        \nThese drinks are often full of added sugars which can be extremely detrimental to your health.</string>
    <string name="a_complete_guide_to_microsoft_team">1). Zoom vs Google Meet vs Microsoft Teams vs Webex Meetings</string>

</resources>